# LUCAS PADILHA FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

### **PERSONAL INFORMATION**

- Praceta Verderena 9, Barreiro
- +351 912 015 235
- lucas\_padilha@icloud.com

# **ABOUT (PROFESSIONAL) ME**

I'm a person passionate for numbers, logical thinking and complex problems. All of my professional experience (in a lot of different fields) was based with this mindset and I'm pretty sure that kind of mind can change wherever environment that I am in.

## **ACADEMIC BACKGROUND**

### Le Wagon - Lisbon (Portugal)

Full-stack web development | 2019

- Ruby on Rails
- Heroku
- C#
- CSS3
- NET
- Javascript
- ASP.NET
- SQL
- node.js
- SQL Server
- Entity Framework

- Git Flow - Bootstrap - GitHub - jQuery

### FMU FISP - São Paulo - SP (Brazil)

Civil Engineering | Feb 2012 . Jan 2015

- Numerical calculation
- Structural calculation
- Physics
- Mathematics

### CNA - São Paulo - SP (Brazil)

English Course | Jan 2009 - Dec 2011

# **LANGUAGES**

Portuguese | ••••••••
English | •••••••

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

### **Software Developer**

Inspire IT Portugal | Jan 2020 - Present (Portugal)

- Development in full-stack (C#, .NET, ASP.NET, HTML, CSS, jQuery and JavaScript)
- SQL Server for database management
- Visual Studio for development

The project that I am in, is GLLG, a platform about education management in Perú. Most of the time, I develop the backend in C# and .NET, using entity framework (is changing to Dapper), and the front-end I am doing with ASP.NET, using HTML and CSS too, and jQuery.

We use JIRA to project management, using Kanban methodology and bitbucket as coding management platform.

### **Logistics and Warehouse's Manager**

Brodheim Group | Jul 2017 - Oct 2019 (Portugal)

- Merchandise management
- Partial and general inventories
- Logistical control between chain stores
- Contacts with suppliers

### **Math and Physics teacher**

Study Center Primavera | Jan 2017 - Jul 2017

- Explanations and classes, in mathematics and physics, for students from the 1st to the 12th grade.

### **Team Coordinator**

Thousand Solutions | Mar 2016 - Jan 2017 (Portugal)

- Direct customer acquisition for energy business contracts
- Manage team for that same function
- Lead daily morning meetings

### Salesperson and Sub-manager

Levi Strauss & CO | Jan 2014 - Dec 2015 (Brazil)

- Team management
- Sale of products to the public

### **PERSONAL PROJECTS**

### **WALD PROJECT**

- Co-fundador do projecto WALD, um software que cria e configura uma aplicação rails do scratch, apenas com o esquema visual da base de dados.

Neste projecto, eu utilizei JavaScript, HTML5 e CSS3 para construir as páginas públicas (404, 500), alertas, confirmações e botões; bootstrap para designs padrão mudando apenas layouts específicos com CSS; GitHub API para autenticação omniauth; Heroku para implantar o webSite em um servidor; e postgresql para a nossa base de dados relacional, Ruby on Rails para todo o back-end, criando um template padrão, e usando intepolação para cada opção escolhida pelo usuário. Veja-nos em:

□ waldproject.com

### **RABBIT**

- Rabbit is a website that simulates AirBnb (giant website that is based on RoR), the site have the same AirBnb functions, rent an animal - in our case - , have the animal card in map (using API from mapbox), different type of user (with authentication for admin and normal user, animations...

In that project, I used HTML5 and CSS3 (with bootstrap also) for the pages design, JavaScript for alerts animations, drag and drop for weekly top5, Heroku to deploy on a host service, SQLite3 for the database and Ruby on Rails for all the back-end.

Check-us on:

☐ https://pet-shop-boys-9000.herokuapp.com/